{
  "results": [
    {
      "answer": "historian", 
      "question": "What was the Greek historian?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "nile river", 
      "question": "What is the name of the river that fed Egyptian civilization for hundreds of years?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "civilization", 
      "question": "What did the Nile feed for hundreds of years?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "nile", 
      "question": "What is the longest river in the world?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "africa", 
      "question": "Where does the equator begin?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "mediterranean sea", 
      "question": "Where does the flow of the Atlantic Ocean end?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "cataracts", 
      "question": "What does the Nile churn with?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "cataract", 
      "question": "What is a waterfall?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "delta", 
      "question": "What is the delta of the Nile?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "silt", 
      "question": "What is the soil near the mouth of a river called?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "river", 
      "question": "What is the delta near?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "nile", 
      "question": "What is the name of the river that divides the delta of the Nile?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "delta", 
      "question": "What is the name of the delta in which the Nile divides into many streams?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "nile", 
      "question": "What is the name of the Nile in the south?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "south", 
      "question": "In what direction is the upper Nile?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "ethiopia", 
      "question": "What country in Ethiopia caused the Nile to flood every summer?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "nile", 
      "question": "What is the name of the river that floods every summer in Ethiopia?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "nile", 
      "question": "What is the name of the river that deposited rich soil along the Nile?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "floods", 
      "question": "What caused the Nile to be flooded?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "crops", 
      "question": "What is the soil fertile for?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "soil", 
      "question": "What is good for growing crops?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "euphrates", 
      "question": "What is the name of the other river that flooded at the same time every year?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "nile river", 
      "question": "What river flooded at the same time every year?"
    }, 
    {
      "answer": "egyptians", 
      "question": "What ancient Egyptians lived in narrow bands of land on each s?"
    }
  ]
}